# Mohammadhosein Shakiba

#### researcher at int-n.info

Mashhad

shakiba@int-n.info

I'm a third-year undergrad at Ferdowsi University of Mashhad, majoring in Cell and Molecular Biology. I'm passionate about neuroscience research and spend my free time doing research synthesis and meta-analysis. I'm also honing my skills in computer science, machine learning, and statistics for scientific and analytical projects.

## Work Experience

#### Researcher

int-n.info

2023 to Present

- Conduct research synthesis and meta-analysis
- · Lead and collaborate with a team of fellow researchers

### **English Teacher**

Safir Language Academy - Tehrān 2022 to 2023

- Taught English to 100+ individuals of all ages using the ESA method
- Developed course materials, schedules, and quizzes
- Completed a Teacher Training course and earned a certificate

#### **Student Intern**

Molecular lab., Institut Pasteur, - Tehrān 2022 to 2022

- Completed a 120-hour on-site program and earned a certificate
- Formulated custom buffers for extraction protocols
- Activities included DNA extraction, RNA extraction, and PCR procedures
- Gained hands-on experience in key laboratory techniques

### Education

# Bachelor of Science in Cell Biology, Minor in Statistics

Ferdowsi University of Mashhad - Mashhad

2021 to Present

# **High School Diploma**

National Organization for Development of Exceptional Talents (Sampad) 2018 to 2021

### Skills

- Python
- R
- SQL
- Git
- · Machine learning
- Math
- Statistics

# Languages

- Persian Fluent
- English Fluent

# Certifications and Licenses

# CS50x (Harvard University)

Introduction to the intellectual enterprises of computer science and the art of programming. https://cs50.harvard.edu/certificates/2fec4b3b-b324-4c23-9b5c-7632bbd40fbe

## **CS50P** (Harvard University)

Introduction to Programming with Python.

https://cs50.harvard.edu/certificates/30c89e28-bb58-46a6-a4d1-ac180ff48c29

# **Cancer Biology (Johns Hopkins University)**

Introduction to the molecular biology of cancer (oncogenes and tumor suppressor genes) as well as the biologic hallmarks of cancer.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/DM3KFBDJXRJT

### Data Analysis with R (Duke University)

Statistical mastery of data analysis including basic data visualization, statistical testing and inference, and linear modeling.

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/BY4U3Y95N9PZ

## **Publications**

### **ORCID**

https://orcid.org/0009-0003-4404-7759

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/abikahs

## Additional Information

### Other Certifications:

Introduction to Genetics and Evolution (Duke University) https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/EK75PXFAQ6S7

Introduction to Psychology (Yale University) https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/336GDCV52Q53

Introduction to Neurobiology (The University of Chicago) https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/SPXWHULGWVWD